♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪
=Rise Again=
=Episode 5=
A barrier?
Mr. Gu, you've got to help me.
Su Wubing must have
set up a barrier outside the study.
I can't get in at all.
Lin Hai.
I thought you were bringing good news.
Mr. Gu.
He is unbearable.
You've got to take him out for me.
Otherwise,
we'll never get the secret formula
of the Longevity Pill.
Speak.
Get lost first.
Mr. Gu.
I told you to get lost.
(Xue Wuhen, Ancient God Sect)
Show what you've got.
Mr. Gu's a busy man.
No time to chit-chat with you.
Mr. Gu, got a moment now?
Master, please sit.
Please.
I wonder about your cultivation level.
Cultivation has four ranks:
Heaven, Earth, Mystic, and Yellow.
Heaven is the highest,
Yellow the lowest.
Heaven-level masters are
one in a hundred years.
Earth-level, barely a few.
As for Mystic-level,
they're already the best of the best.
Master, and you...?
I've reached early Mystic-level.
Good.
Are you dead yet?
Pay up.
With your cultivation, Master,
I'm impressed.
Hurry up.
Here's 500,000 dollars.
I want someone dead.
(Since ancient times,)
(my ancestors have traveled
through time into this world,)
(founding the Ancient God Sect,)
(just to seize the souls of
the Immortal King and Holy Maiden.)
(Never thought I'd actually
run into them.)
- Pleasure doing business.
Master, wait!
Besides having
a sickly old mother,
Su Wubing also has a childhood friend.
Got it.
Dad's illness is cured,
but Gu Yuanbing won't
let it go so easily.
What did my dad say to you yesterday?
Uncle Lin said
you should marry me.
Marry you?
Or rather,
I'm marrying into the Lin family.
Dad wants you to protect me?
I used to think,
I needed no one
to protect me in this world.
The world is vast,
and I can do whatever I want.
But after this,
maybe
I was wrong.
Whatever you want to do,
I'll support you.
Easy to say.
(Didn't expect the curse
to grow stronger.)
(Why do I feel so strangely close to him?)
Not good.
What are you afraid of?
Why did you
bring me here?
Don't worry,
you're just bait.
It's Su Wubing I want.
You...
Are you going after him?
Little girl,
it's not "going after".
I just want his life.
Let her go!
Wubing.
He's coming for you.
It's fine, you go first.
Finally, you're here.
Truly worthy of being the Immortal King.
Even your mortal body has such an aura.
The souls of the Immortal King
and Holy Maiden...
Follow them, seize their souls,
and our demons will
rule the Immortal Realm.
(So the demons also entered
the Time-Space Array.)
Su Wubing?
What is he doing here?
Seems you've been hunting me all along.
We've sought you for ten thousand years,
and finally, it wasn't in vain.
You may be an ancient Immortal King,
but now you're only Yellow-level.
Perfect time to take your soul.
I'll let you
have three moves.
Ancient God Sect,
acting for Heaven.
Today I'll take your life.
The Immortal King just awoke.
I must strike a killing blow.
First move.
Impossible.
That move
should've drained
all your spiritual power.
Second move.
You... you're not Yellow-level?
Three moves are done.
Kneel
or die.
No way!
Still stubborn.
Fall.
So it's really you.
♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪